

# Subhransu Maharana

Full Stack Engineer



+91 9886326216



subhransumaharana@gmail.com



subhnet.github.io



https://github.com/subhnet



Sarjapura Road,Bengaluru, India 560035



# **ABOUT ME**

An Experienced Full-Stack Developer with six years of experience in designing, developing and implementing applications and solutions using range of technologies. Always keen to learn new technologies, Following best Quality Practices by applying Design Patterns, on-time Delivery, and looking to take more leadership over project delivery.



# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### **Full Stack Engineer**

June, 2019 - present

#### **Adobe Systems**

- Worked on building executive focused Adobe analytics dashboards for Adobe's top digital marketing clients.
- Worked on developing custom web applications end to end to solve various customer needs.
- Designed and Developed an Automation Framework that automates the
  processing of onboarding a client to Adobe Analytics, Launch and Target
  for a Cutomer Website. This Framework reduced the Consultant Efforts
  significantly by 90% and Is now used widely across the teams.
- Worked with tight deadlines, and small consulting budgets to complete major tasks.

Server Side: **Node.Js**, **Express.Js**, **Java**, **Docker**, **AWS**, GraphQL Client Side: **ReactJS**, Javascript, HTML, CSS

### **Software Engineer**

March, 2017 - May, 2019

# **Fidelity Investments**

- Responsible for upgrading the code base to Angular UI and Back-end in JAVA Restful Services. Developing testable, reusable and maintainable components/services, integrating Restful API's.
- Responsible for the development of a Table Component Framework for eTax Application, which made a rendering of dynamic content customizable, focusing on its stability. It was reused across Multiple teams as well.
- Implemented Lazy-Loading, leading to an 85% reduction in web app loading time.
- Identified and suggested new technologies and tools for enhancing product value

## **Project Engineer**

Sept, 2014 - Feb, 2017

### **Wipro Technologies**

Bluedart Website Revamp

- Key Contributor in development and implementation of an appropriate design pattern.
- Development of SOAP-based Web Services (bottom-up) which internally consumes various third-party vendors and also calls Oracle stored procedures.
- Google Map API Integration with shortest path implementation
- Worked on Module end to end (UI layer using LiferayAUI, Controllers and Client Stub using axis2 implementation)



## SKILLS

#### FRONT END

- ReactJS, AngularJS
- HTML5, CSS
- Javascript(ES5,ES6)
- Typescript
- JQuery

#### **BACK END**

- Java
- Node.JS, NPM
- ExpressJs
- Spring Framework
- SpringBoot
- MySQL
- Serverless Framework

#### **DEVOPS**

- AWS
- Docker
- Apache Openwhisk
- Apache Airflow

# MISCELLANEOUS SKILLS

GraphQL Git Tomcat NGINX Maven Webpack Babel Rest API



#### **ACHIEVEMENT**

**"On the Spot Award"** - Awarded in Fidelity Investments, 2017.

**"Individual Award"** - Awarded for solving complex framework bugs in Fidelity, 2018.

"Team of the Quarter" -

Awarded for contribution in Adobe, 2020



# **EDUCATION**

# **B.Tech in Computer Science**

Veer Surendra Sai University of Technology 2010-2014